Guide to the Ellen McGowan Biddle Shipman papers, 1914-1946.
Shipman, Ellen McGowan Biddle papers, 1914-1946.
- Series IV. Project Files (Plans)
  - Mrs. Baroness Maud Ledyard von Kettcher (Map-case Folder 158)
    - Construction drawing, 1945 (Map-case Folder 158)
    - Lawn planting plan, 1945 (Map-case Folder 158)
    - Sketches, 1945 (Map-case Folder 158)
    - Planting plan for flower garden (Blueprint), 1945 (Map-case Folder 158)
    - Garden grading and development plan, 1945 (Map-case Folder 158)
    - Alterations and additions to residence, 1945 (Map-case Folder 158)
  - Mr. and Mrs. R.T. Vanderbilt (Map-case Folder 159-160)
    Location: Green Farm, Connecticut
    - Bulb planting plan for magnolia terrace, 1939 (Map-case Folder 159)
    - Bulb planting plan for entrance, 1939 (Map-case Folder 159)
    - Driveway planting - Section A and B, 1939 (Map-case Folder 159)
    - Perennial planting plan for gardens, 1939 (Map-case Folder 159)
    - Planting plan for entrance, 1939 (Map-case Folder 159)
    - Bulb planting plan for ravine, 1939 (Map-case Folder 159)
    - Plot plan, 1939 (Map-case Folder 159)
    - Construction plan for wall niche in flower garden, 1939 (Map-case Folder 159)
    - Planting plans for boundary wall - Section A-C, 1939 (Map-case Folder 159)
    - Construction plan for flower garden, 1939 (Map-case Folder 159)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan for flower garden (VOID), 1940 (Map-case Folder 159)
    - Planting plan for magnolia garden, 1940 (Map-case Folder 159)
    - Tree and planting plan for ravine, 1940 (Map-case Folder 159)
    - Ground cover planting plan for ravine (Blueprint), 1940 (Map-case Folder 159)
    - Plantint plan for north and west terrace, 1940 (Map-case Folder 159)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan for the flower garden, 1940 (Map-case Folder 159)
    - Bulb planting plan for flower garden, 1940 (Map-case Folder 159)
    - Revised ground cover planting plan for lower ravine, 1940 (Map-case Folder 159)
    - Revised shrub planting plan for lower ravine, 1940 (Map-case Folder 160)
    - Bulb planting plan for terrace, 1940 (Map-case Folder 160)
    - Plan of ravine paths, 1940 (Map-case Folder 160)
    - Construction drawings for well and well head, 1940 (Map-case Folder 160)
    - Construction drawings for stone seat A and B in ravine, 1940 (Map-case Folder 160)
    - Construction drawings for stone seat in flower garden, 1940 (Map-case Folder 160)
    - Construction drawing for millstone bird bath, 1940 (Map-case Folder 160)
    - Plan of stone path, 1940 (Map-case Folder 160)
    - Plan for staking out garden, 1940 (Map-case Folder 160)
    - Design plan of flower garden, 1940 (Map-case Folder 160)
    - ketch of wall niche, 1940 (Map-case Folder 160)
    - Revised design plan (x2), 1940 (Map-case Folder 160)
    - Construction drawing for flower garden, 1940 (Map-case Folder 160)
    - Map of precise and topographic survey (Blueprint), 1940 (Map-case Folder 160)
    - Residence (2 Blueprints), 1940 (Map-case Folder 160)
    - Map of land west of ravine (Blueprint), 1940 (Map-case Folder 160)
    - Proposed landscape plan (White print and Blueprint), 1940 (Map-case Folder 160)
    - Revised construction plan for north terrace, 1940 (Map-case Folder 160)
  - Mrs. A.L. West (Map-case Folder 161)
    - Preliminary sketch A (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 161)
    - Preliminary design sketch B and C (Map-case Folder 161)
  - Mrs. C.S. Williams (Map-case Folder 161)
    - Planting plan for flower beds, 1934 (Map-case Folder 161)
    - Construction plan for wall and niche, 1934 (Map-case Folder 161)
    - Revised construction plan showing location of proposed brick wall, 1934 (Map-case Folder 161)
    - Construction details for gate in garden, 1934 (Map-case Folder 161)
    - Plan for planting flower beds, 1934 (Map-case Folder 161)
    - Dimension plan for parterre beds, 1934 (Map-case Folder 161)
    - Details of compass, 1934 (Map-case Folder 161)
    - Roses, perennials, and annuals planting plan - Section A, 1934 (Map-case Folder 161)
    - Ground covers planting plan - Section A, 1934 (Map-case Folder 161)
    - Construction details for wall fountain, 1934 (Map-case Folder 161)
    - Preliminary design plan, 1934 (Map-case Folder 161)
    - Revised design plan, 1934 (Map-case Folder 161)
    - Trees and shrubs planting plan - Sections A and B, 1934 (Map-case Folder 161)
    - Construction details for pedestal for bird bath, 1934 (Map-case Folder 161)
  - Windsor T. White (Map-case Folder 162; 199-201)
    Location: Hunting Valley, (Chagrin Falls; Halfred Farms), Ohio
    - Planting plan I and II for flower garden (photocopy), 1920 (Map-case Folder 162)
    - Shrub and bulb planting plan (photocopy), 1921 (Map-case Folder 162)
    - Shrub and tree planting plan (photocopy), 1921 (Map-case Folder 162)
    - Construction plan of garden, 1920 (Map-case Folder 162)
    - Design of iris garden, 1920 (Map-case Folder 162)
    - General plan for grounds, 1920 (Map-case Folder 162)
    - Sketch plan of planting and garden, 1920 (Map-case Folder 162)
    - Sketch for bridge, 1920 (Map-case Folder 162)
    - Construction plan for iris garden, 1920 (Map-case Folder 162)
    - Planting plan for iris garden (photocopy), 1931 (Map-case Folder 162)
    - Construction plan for flower garden, 1920 (Map-case Folder 162)
    - Proposed new entrance road, 1920 (Map-case Folder 162)
    - Plan for change in driveway - Sketch 3, 1920 (Map-case Folder 162)
    - Plan and section of pool and seat (photocopy), 1919 (Map-case Folder 162)
    - Bridge detail (Blueprint), 1920 (Map-case Folder 162)
    - Construction plan for stone seat, 1920 (Map-case Folder 162)
    - Construction plan for pool in iris garden, 1920 (Map-case Folder 162)
    - Construction drawing of gate (Blueprint), 1920 (Map-case Folder 162)
    - First and second floor plans of the original farm house at Halfred Farms, Undated (Map-case Folder 199)
      Note on reverse reads that these plans pre-date Edward A. Merritt
    - Construction plan for stone seat in wall (Blueprint), Undated (Map-case Folder 200)
    - Halfred Farms Aerial Survey, 1939 (Map-case Folder 200)
    - Construction plan for pool in the iris garden (2 Blueprints), 1931 (Map-case Folder 200)
    - General layout of guest wing garden and bath house (Blueprint), 1939 (Map-case Folder 200)
    - Specifications for bathing pavilion (3 typewritten pages), Undated (Map-case Folder 200)
    - Construction plan for iris garden (2 Blueprints), 1931 (Map-case Folder 200)
    - Planting plan for iris garden (2 Blueprints), 1931 (Map-case Folder 200)
    - Sketch of planting plan for iris garden (2 Photocopies), Undated (Map-case Folder 200)
    - Unlabelled sketch (Photocopy), Undated (Map-case Folder 200)
    - Cellar, East and West Elevations (Blueprints), Undated (Map-case Folder 200)
    - Plans, elevations and sections of bathing pavilion (2 Blueprints), 1920 (Map-case Folder 201)
    - Bulb planting plan (Blueprint), 1921 (Map-case Folder 201)
    - Plans for stone bridge (Blueprint), 1931 (Map-case Folder 201)
      Note on reverse states that the bridge was destroyed in 1994.
    - Construction for the flower garden (3 Blueprints), 1921 (Map-case Folder 201)
    - Planting plan I for flower garden (Blueprints and Linen), 1921 (Map-case Folder 201)
    - Shrub planting plan around garage (3 Blueprints and 1 Linen), Undated (Map-case Folder 201)
    - Planting plan II for flower garden (Blueprint and Linen), 1920 (Map-case Folder 201)
    - Typographical map of property (A.D. Taylor, Landscape Architect), c. 1949 (Map-case Folder 201)
    - Perennial Garden Existing Conditions Alfred M. Rankin Property (originally drawn for Windsor White in 1921), c. 1983 (Map-case Folder 201)
  - Mrs. S.D. Warren (Map-case Folder 162)
    Location: Mattapoisett, Massachusetts
    - Plan showing changes in garden, 1912 (Map-case Folder 162)
    - Planting plan, 1912 (Map-case Folder 162)
    - Preliminary sketch of garden, 1912 (Map-case Folder 162)
    - Construction plan of garden, 1912 (Map-case Folder 162)
    - Detail of lily pond, 1912 (Map-case Folder 162)
    - Detail drawing of fence around service court, 1912 (Map-case Folder 162)
  - Clark Williams (Map-case Folder 163)
    Location: Lee County, South Carolina
    - Plan of garden, 1925 (Map-case Folder 163)
    - General design plan, 1927 (Map-case Folder 163)
    - Preliminary design plan on estate, 1927 (Map-case Folder 163)
    - Shrub planting plan, 1927 (Map-case Folder 163)
    - Perennial planting plan, 1927 (Map-case Folder 163)
    - Diagram of proposed location of buildings, 1927 (Map-case Folder 163)
    - Perennial planting plan for flower garden, 1928 (Map-case Folder 163)
    - Plan of rose garden (Map-case Folder 163)
  - Mrs. Clark Williams (Map-case Folder 163-164)
    - Sketch for placing central figure, 1927 (Map-case Folder 163)
    - Perennial planting plan - Sections 1 and 2 (Map-case Folder 163)
    - Shrub planting plan for blue garden - Section 1 (Blueprint), 1926 (Map-case Folder 163)
    - Bulb planting plan for rose garden (2 Blueprints, 1 Black and White), 1925 (Map-case Folder 163)
    - Bulb planting plan for blue garden (2 Blueprints, 1 Black and White), 1925 (Map-case Folder 163)
    - Bulb planting plan for old fashioned garden (2 Blueprints, 1 Black and White), 1925 (Map-case Folder 163)
    - Bulb planting plan for pink garden (2 Blueprints, 1 Black and White), 1925 (Map-case Folder 163)
    - Planting plan for oval pool (Map-case Folder 163)
    - Plan for pool (Map-case Folder 163)
    - Sketch plan for garden (Map-case Folder 163)
    - Construction plan for garden (Map-case Folder 163)
    - Paved terrace for garden (Map-case Folder 163)
    - General shrub planting plan, 1926 (Map-case Folder 163)
    - Memorandum for placing box, 1927 (Map-case Folder 164)
    - Bulb planting plans - Sections 1-4 (Map-case Folder 164)
    - Plan for the Peony border (Map-case Folder 164)
    - Shrub planting plan for pink garden (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 164)
    - Perennial planting plan - Sections 3 and 4 (Map-case Folder 164)
    - Perennial planting plan for blue garden - Section 1 (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 164)
    - Perennial planting plan for pink garden - Section 2 (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 164)
    - Perennial planting plan for rose garden - Section 3 (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 164)
    - Flower planting plan for old fashioned garden, 1926 (Map-case Folder 164)
    - Shrub planting plan, 1926 (Map-case Folder 164)
    - Construction details for garden steps and wall, 1926 (Map-case Folder 164)
    - Construction plan for square pool, 1926 (Map-case Folder 164)
    - Construction plan for oval pool, 1926 (Map-case Folder 164)
    - Sketch of garden, 1926 (Map-case Folder 164)
    - Garden corner layout, 1926 (Map-case Folder 164)
    - Shrub planting plan for old fashioned garden (Blueprint), 1926 (Map-case Folder 164)
  - Oscar Weber (Map-case Folder 165-167)
    - Perennial planting plan for green panel garden, 1930 (Map-case Folder 165)
    - Revised tree and shrub planting plan for terraces and turnarounds, 1930 (Map-case Folder 165)
    - Shrub planting plan, 1930 (Map-case Folder 165)
    - Survey (Blueprint), 1930 (Map-case Folder 165)
    - Sketch of an evergreen garden, 1930 (Map-case Folder 165)
    - Revised planting plan of service court, 1930 (Map-case Folder 165)
    - Preliminary plan of garden, 1930 (Map-case Folder 165)
    - Layout plan pf green panel garden, 1930 (Map-case Folder 165)
    - Construction plan of service court, 1930 (Map-case Folder 165)
    - Sketch for lamp on terrace (2 copies and photostats), 1930 (Map-case Folder 165)
    - Preliminary sketch A, 1930 (Map-case Folder 165)
    - Shrub and vine planting plan, 1930 (Map-case Folder 165)
    - Design along stream, 1930 (Map-case Folder 165)
    - Revised design along stream, 1930 (Map-case Folder 165)
    - Planting for border of circular pool, 1930 (Map-case Folder 165)
    - Sketches, 1930 (Map-case Folder 165)
    - First floor plan of residence (Blueprint), 1930 (Map-case Folder 165)
    - Planting plan for rose garden, 1930 (Map-case Folder 165)
    - Plan about residence (Blueprint), 1930 (Map-case Folder 165)
    - General construction plan for terrace and turnaround, 1930 (Map-case Folder 165)
    - Details of stone grilles in garden, 1930 (Map-case Folder 165)
    - Details of gates in garden, 1930 (Map-case Folder 165)
    - Detail of wood post at junction of wall and house, 1930 (Map-case Folder 165)
    - Key plan of planting plans (Black and White), 1930 (Map-case Folder 166)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan for south boundary - plan B, 1930 (Map-case Folder 166)
    - Lake front elevation sketch 1-4, 1930 (Map-case Folder 166)
    - Sketch for wooden seat, 1930 (Map-case Folder 166)
    - General layout for evergreen garden, 1930 (Map-case Folder 166)
    - Sketch plan and elevation of garden, 1930 (Map-case Folder 166)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan, 1930 (Map-case Folder 166)
    - Plan of south east portion of gardens (Blueprint), 1930 (Map-case Folder 166)
    - Revised planting plan of entrance (Blueprint), 1930 (Map-case Folder 166)
    - General tree and shrub planting plan for front lawn, 1930 (Map-case Folder 166)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan for green panel garden, 1930 (Map-case Folder 166)
    - Sketch for seat, 1930 (Map-case Folder 166)
    - Construction plan for flagstone paving, 1930 (Map-case Folder 166)
    - Sketch of existing garden cover, 1930 (Map-case Folder 166)
    - Details of terrace balustrade, 1930 (Map-case Folder 166)
    - Revised design plan for rose garden, 1930 (Map-case Folder 166)
    - Construction plan of terrace wall, 1930 (Map-case Folder 166)
    - Construction plan for stone seat, 1930 (Map-case Folder 166)
    - Revised sketch for seat, 1930 (Map-case Folder 166)
    - Sketch of evergreen garden, 1930 (Map-case Folder 167)
    - Design plan for green panel garden, 1930 (Map-case Folder 167)
    - Design plan for stone seat, 1930 (Map-case Folder 167)
    - Alternate design for entrance turn, 1930 (Map-case Folder 167)
    - Plan from survey (Blueprint), 1930 (Map-case Folder 167)
    - Bulb planting plan for rose garden, 1930 (Map-case Folder 167)
    - Bulb planting plan for green panel garden, 1930 (Map-case Folder 167)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan for the bowl, 1930 (Map-case Folder 167)
    - Layout plan for the rose garden, 1930 (Map-case Folder 167)
    - Detail plan of entrance drive (Blueprint), 1930 (Map-case Folder 167)
    - Shrub planting plan for service court, 1930 (Map-case Folder 167)
    - Detail of stone terrace piers, 1930 (Map-case Folder 167)
    - Suggested design plan 1 and 2, 1930 (Map-case Folder 167)
    - Sketch design for wrought iron gate, 1930 (Map-case Folder 167)
    - Planting plan for north west side of the house, 1930 (Map-case Folder 167)
    - Shrub and vine planting plan for north west side of the house, 1930 (Map-case Folder 167)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan for south boundary - plan A, 1930 (Map-case Folder 167)
  - Mr. and Mrs. James Winston (Map-case Folder 168)
    - 3 sketches, 1939 (Map-case Folder 168)
    - Preliminary design plan (and White print), 1939 (Map-case Folder 168)
    - Revised plot plan (White print), 1939 (Map-case Folder 168)
    - Plot plan (Blueprint), 1939 (Map-case Folder 168)
    - Outline floor plan (White print), 1939 (Map-case Folder 168)
    - Entrance court planting plan, 1939 (Map-case Folder 168)
    - Plan for trees and shrubs around the house, 1939 (Map-case Folder 168)
  - Laurence Williams (Map-case Folder 168)
    - Plot plan (White print) (Map-case Folder 168)
    - Property survey (White print) (Map-case Folder 168)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 168)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Edward Weston (Map-case Folder 168)
    Location: Montclair, New Jersey
    - General plan (White print) (Map-case Folder 168)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 168)
    - Planting plan for ground covers for wild garden (Map-case Folder 168)
    - Plan for staking out paths in wild garden (Map-case Folder 168)
  - Dr. and Mrs. Orrin Wightman (Map-case Folder 168)
    - Planting plan (Map-case Folder 168)
  - Richard A. Wood (or Woods) (Map-case Folder 168)
    - Topographic map - (2 White prints, Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 168)
    - 2 sketches (Map-case Folder 168)
  - Samuel H. Watts (Map-case Folder 168)
    - Garden wall (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 168)
      Cameron Clark, architect
  - R. Wilbur (Map-case Folder 168)
    - Plan and section of pool in garden (Map-case Folder 168)
  - Mrs. Edward Warren (Map-case Folder 169)
    Location: Waverly, Pennsylvania
    - Sketches for wooden gate in terrace wall (Map-case Folder 169)
    - Details of garden gate (Map-case Folder 169)
    - Alternative design sketch (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 169)
    - General construction plan (Map-case Folder 169)
    - Contour map of part of property (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 169)
    - Preliminary design plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 169)
    - Construction plan and detail of drying yard and lath fence (Map-case Folder 169)
    - Shrub planting plan (Map-case Folder 169)
  - Mr. Holden White (Map-case Folder 169)
    - Layout plan for driveway (Map-case Folder 169)
    - General design plan (Map-case Folder 169)
    - Plans of residence (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 169)
    - Topographic survey (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 169)
    - Topographic map (2 Blueprints) (Map-case Folder 169)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Thomas White (Map-case Folder 170)
    - Preliminary sketch of garden (Map-case Folder 170)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 170)
    - Planting plan of garden (Map-case Folder 170)
    - Construction plan of garden (Map-case Folder 170)
  - Superintendent's garden at the U.S. Military Academy (Map-case Folder 170)
    Location: West Point, New York
    - Plan of garden (Blueprint), 1936 (Map-case Folder 170)
    - Sketch, undated (Map-case Folder 170)
    - Perennial planting plan, 1936 (Map-case Folder 170)
    - General construction plan, 1936 (Map-case Folder 170)
    - Detail drawing for sandstone bowls, 1936 (Map-case Folder 170)
    - Revisions of stone base for fountain, undated (Map-case Folder 170)
    - Trees and shrubs planting plan - Sheet A and B, 1936 (Map-case Folder 170)
    - Bulb planting plan - Sheet A and B (Map-case Folder 170)
    - Preliminary design plan (Black and White), undated (Map-case Folder 170)
    - Rough sketches, high plants, undated (Map-case Folder 170)
    - Sketches of plantings (x2), undated (Map-case Folder 170)
    - List of plants, undated (Map-case Folder 170)
    - Sketch of garden with plants listed, undated (Map-case Folder 170)
    - Perennial planting plan - Sheet B, 1936 (Map-case Folder 170)
    - Construction details for wall fountain and pool, 1936 (Map-case Folder 170)
  - Albert R. Whittier (Map-case Folder 171)
    Location: Milton, Massachusetts
    - Tree and shrub planting plan (2 Blueprints) (Map-case Folder 171)
    - Shrub planting plan for southeast bank (Map-case Folder 171)
    - Topographic survey (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 171)
    - Bulb planting plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 171)
    - Perennial planting plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 171)
    - Plans of residence (Blueprints) (Map-case Folder 171)
    - Contour plan of embankment (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 171)
    - Sketch plan of entrance court showing trees (2 Blueprints) (Map-case Folder 171)
    - Planting plan of entrance court (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 171)
    - General design plan (Map-case Folder 171)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Frederick Warburg (Map-case Folder 172)
    - Plan residence (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 172)
    - Corrections to grading plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 172)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 172)
    - Grading plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 172)
    - Terrace details (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 172)
    - Construction drawing for terrace walls and seat (Map-case Folder 172)
    - Trees and shrubs planting plan (Map-case Folder 172)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Reynolds Wilson (Map-case Folder 173)
    - Preliminary plan (2 Black and white) (Map-case Folder 173)
    - House plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 173)
    - House elevation (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 173)
    - Topographical plan of Meeds farm (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 173)
    - Topographical plan of Mundy farm (Photostat) (Map-case Folder 173)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 173)
    - Topographic map of property (2 Black and White) (Map-case Folder 173)
    - Revised design plan (Map-case Folder 173)
  - Mrs. E.V.K. Willson (Map-case Folder 173)
    - General design plan (Map-case Folder 173)
    - Construction plan for terrace (Map-case Folder 173)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 173)
    - General construction plan and details (Map-case Folder 173)
    - Topographic plan of property (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 173)
    - Grading plan for entrance drive (Map-case Folder 173)
    - Plan of residence (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 173)
  - Mrs. Stafford Wrightman (Map-case Folder 173)
    - Construction drawing for garden (Map-case Folder 173)
    - Plot plan (Map-case Folder 173)
  - Mrs. Allan Wood (Map-case Folder 173)
    - Construction details for pool (Map-case Folder 173)
    - Sketch of pool (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 173)
    - Revised design incorporating pool (Map-case Folder 173)
    - Construction plan of garden (Map-case Folder 173)
    - Preliminary design sketch 1-3 (Map-case Folder 173)
    - Construction plan of garden (Blueprint) (VOID) (Map-case Folder 173)
  - Mrs. Margaret W. Weld (Map-case Folder 174)
    - Topographic and tree plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 174)
    - Plot plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 174)
    - Preliminary plan for bridge (Map-case Folder 174)
    - Suggested design for garden (Map-case Folder 174)
    - Construction plan for garden (Map-case Folder 174)
    - Sketch (Map-case Folder 174)
    - Preliminary design 1-4 (Map-case Folder 174)
    - General construction plan (Map-case Folder 174)
    - Bulb plating plan (Map-case Folder 174)
    - General design plan (Map-case Folder 174)
    - Shrub planting plan for garden (Map-case Folder 174)
    - Perennial planting plan for garden (Map-case Folder 174)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 174)
    - Shrub plating plan for garden (Map-case Folder 174)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 174)
    - Shrub planting plan for entrance (Map-case Folder 174)
    - Shrub planting plan for roadside and brook (Map-case Folder 174)
    - Construction data for grass terrace (Map-case Folder 174)
    - Planting plan to screen drying yard (Map-case Folder 174)
  - Mrs. H.H. Weiss (Map-case Folder 174)
    - General design plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 174)
    - Plot plan (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 174)
  - Lundsford P. Yandell (Map-case Folder 175)
    - First floor plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 175)
    - Topography (Map-case Folder 175)
    - Design plan (White print) (Map-case Folder 175)
    - Sketches (Map-case Folder 175)
    - Survey of property (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 175)
    - Basement plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 175)
    - Front elevation (Map-case Folder 175)
    - Rear elevation (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 175)
    - Section (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 175)
    - Revised topography (Map-case Folder 175)
    - Trees, shrubs, and vines planting plan (Map-case Folder 175)
    - Construction drawings for garden gate (Map-case Folder 175)
    - Construction plan for terraces (Map-case Folder 175)
    - Plan for layout of beds and paths in flower garden (Map-case Folder 175)
    - Construction drawing for walls in the flower garden (Map-case Folder 175)
    - Plan showing proposed grades around the house (Map-case Folder 175)
    - Plan for shrubs and vines around the house (Map-case Folder 175)